{"data":[{"question":"The officials object to them wearing long dresses for the inaugural dance at the country club.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to","b":"them","c":"wearing","d":"at the country club","answer":"2","explain":" - Them-> x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Janet is finally used to cook on an electric stove after having a gas one for so long.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"cook","b":"after having","c":"one","d":"for so long","answer":"1","explain":" - Cook-> cooking","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"He knows to repair the carburetor without talking the whole car apart.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"knows","b":"the","c":"talking","d":"apart","answer":"3","explain":" - Talking-> taking","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Stuart stopped to write his letter because he had to leave for the hospital.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"to write","b":"because","c":"leave","d":"for the hospital","answer":"1","explain":" - To write-> writting","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"She must retyping the report before she hands it in to the director of financing.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"retyping","b":"before","c":"hands it in","d":"to the","answer":"1","explain":" - Retyping-> retype","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"How much times did Rich and Jennifer have to do the experiment before they obtained the results they had been expecting.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"much","b":"did Rich and Jennifer have to","c":"obtained the results","d":"been expecting","answer":"1","explain":" - Much-> many","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Each of the students in the accounting class has to type their own research paper this semester.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"students","b":"in the","c":"their","d":"own","answer":"3","explain":" - Their-> his\/her","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Mrs. Stevens, along with her cousins from New Mexico, are planning to attend the festivities.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"with","b":"her cousins from","c":"are","d":"to attend","answer":"3","explain":" - Are-> is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"They are going to have to leave soon, and so do we.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are","b":"to have to","c":"leave soon","d":"so do","answer":"4","explain":" - So do-> so are","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"All the students are looking forward spending their free time relaxing in the sun this summer.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"students","b":"are","c":"forward spending","d":"their","answer":"3","explain":" - Forward spending-> forward to spending","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"25","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"}]}